Tufts Weekly UP056
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Tufts Weekly, 1895 -- 1968; UP056.001; 2.4 Linear Feet; 62 Volumes; 19.78 Gigabytes; 2079 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 28, 1917; UP056.001.008.00055; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.89 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 7, 1917; UP056.001.008.00056; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.50 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 14, 1917; UP056.001.008.00057; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.67 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 21, 1917; UP056.001.008.00058; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.91 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 28, 1917; UP056.001.008.00059; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.91 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 4, 1917; UP056.001.008.00060; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.70 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 11, 1917; UP056.001.008.00061; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.21 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 2, 1917; UP056.001.008.00062; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.76 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 9, 1917; UP056.001.008.00063; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.74 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 16, 1917; UP056.001.008.00064; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.24 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 23, 1917; UP056.001.008.00065; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.17 Megabytes (Box 8)
    Additional user copies in the Reading Room. All Around Club.
  - Tufts Weekly, May 30, 1917; UP056.001.008.00066; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.30 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 20, 1917; UP056.001.008.00067; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.69 Megabytes (Box 8)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 10, 1917; UP056.001.009.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.10 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 17, 1917; UP056.001.009.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.48 Megabytes (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni] Graduates in every state
  - Tufts Weekly, October 24, 1917; UP056.001.009.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.54 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 31, 1917; UP056.001.009.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.47 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 7, 1917; UP056.001.009.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.48 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 14, 1917; UP056.001.009.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.92 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 21, 1917; UP056.001.009.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.96 Megabytes (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Academic Honors, 1913- 1920 p.1,3.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 28, 1917; UP056.001.009.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.56 Megabytes (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Academic Honors, 1913- 1920 p.1,6.
  - Tufts Weekly, December 5, 1917; UP056.001.009.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.81 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 12, 1917; UP056.001.009.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 10.40 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 9, 1918; UP056.001.009.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.94 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 16, 1918; UP056.001.009.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.77 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 23, 1918; UP056.001.009.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.88 Megabytes (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, January 30, 1918; UP056.001.009.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.50 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 6, 1918; UP056.001.009.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.28 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 13, 1918; UP056.001.009.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.45 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 20, 1918; UP056.001.009.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.77 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 27, 1918; UP056.001.009.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.02 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 6, 1918; UP056.001.009.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.99 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 13, 1918; UP056.001.009.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.11 Megabytes (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Alumni trustees
  - Tufts Weekly, March 20, 1918; UP056.001.009.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.48 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 27, 1918; UP056.001.009.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.74 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 3, 1918; UP056.001.009.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.29 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 10, 1918; UP056.001.009.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.14 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 17, 1918; UP056.001.009.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.40 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 24, 1918; UP056.001.009.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.93 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 1, 1918; UP056.001.009.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.63 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 8, 1918; UP056.001.009.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.36 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 15, 1918; UP056.001.009.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.39 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 22, 1918; UP056.001.009.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.29 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 29, 1918; UP056.001.009.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.94 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 12, 1918; UP056.001.009.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.21 Megabytes (Box 9)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 23, 1918; UP056.001.010.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.74 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 30, 1918; UP056.001.010.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.57 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room. The Tuftonian Vol. 2, no. 1- 1871-1877 Tufts College, MA All Around Club.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 6, 1918; UP056.001.010.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.87 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 13, 1918; UP056.001.010.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.78 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 20, 1918; UP056.001.010.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.68 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 27, 1918; UP056.001.010.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.98 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room. All Around Club.
  - Tufts Weekly, December 4, 1918; UP056.001.010.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.63 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 11, 1918; UP056.001.010.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.54 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room. Alumni association A.W. Coolidge [A1903] appointed secretary
  - Tufts Weekly, January 1, 1919; UP056.001.010.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.87 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room. All Around Club; [Alumni association] Executive committee
  - Tufts Weekly, January 8, 1919; UP056.001.010.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.25 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room. Academic Honors, 1913- 1920 p.3.
  - Tufts Weekly, January 15, 1919; UP056.001.010.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.40 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 22, 1919; UP056.001.010.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.46 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 29, 1919; UP056.001.010.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.85 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 5, 1919; UP056.001.010.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.26 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room. All Around Club. Death of (1/31/19) Windom A. Allen (1915) in service (Hero Sons of Tufts) (Makes 16th gold star for Tufts).
  - Tufts Weekly, February 12, 1919; UP056.001.010.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.42 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 19, 1919; UP056.001.010.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.23 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, February 26, 1919; UP056.001.010.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.99 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 5, 1919; UP056.001.010.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.80 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 12, 1919; UP056.001.010.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.99 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 19, 1919; UP056.001.010.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 10.18 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 2, 1919; UP056.001.010.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.60 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room. Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 9, 1919; UP056.001.010.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.90 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 16, 1919; UP056.001.010.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.11 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room. Alumni trustees
  - Tufts Weekly, April 23, 1919; UP056.001.010.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.71 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 30, 1919; UP056.001.010.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.49 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 7, 1919; UP056.001.010.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.81 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room. Death of (10/15/18) Philip Algar (D 1919) in service (Hero Sons of Tufts).
  - Tufts Weekly, May 14, 1919; UP056.001.010.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.08 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 21, 1919; UP056.001.010.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.43 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 28, 1919; UP056.001.010.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.28 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room. All Around Club. Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, June 4, 1919; UP056.001.010.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.97 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 11, 1919; UP056.001.010.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.94 Megabytes (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in Reading Room. All Around Club. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, June 25, 1919; UP056.001.010.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 14.36 Megabytes (Box 10)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 1, 1919; UP056.001.011.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.33 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 8, 1919; UP056.001.011.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.79 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 15, 1919; UP056.001.011.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.54 Megabytes (Box 11)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. All Around Club; [Alumni] E.D. Sabine [A1896] what the alumni do to aid the hill
  - Tufts Weekly, October 22, 1919; UP056.001.011.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.26 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 29, 1919; UP056.001.011.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.31 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 5, 1919; UP056.001.011.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.39 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 12, 1919; UP056.001.011.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.17 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 19, 1919; UP056.001.011.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.62 Megabytes (Box 11)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Academic Honors, 1913-1920. pp. 1,6.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 26, 1919; UP056.001.011.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.13 Megabytes (Box 11)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. AMRAD [American Radio and Research Corporation] erecting new plant, p 4
  - Tufts Weekly, December 3, 1919; UP056.001.011.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.20 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 10, 1919; UP056.001.011.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.74 Megabytes (Box 11)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. All Around Club. Alpha Omicron Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, December 17, 1919; UP056.001.011.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.06 Megabytes (Box 11)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. All Around Club. Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, January 7, 1920; UP056.001.011.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.27 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 14, 1920; UP056.001.011.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.20 Megabytes (Box 11)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, January 21, 1920; UP056.001.011.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.45 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 28, 1920; UP056.001.011.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.60 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 11, 1920; UP056.001.011.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.59 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 18, 1920; UP056.001.011.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.62 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 25, 1920; UP056.001.011.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.31 Megabytes (Box 11)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. All Around Club. Alpha Tau Omega; [Alumni] E.D. Sabine [A1896] what the alumni do to aid the hill
  - Tufts Weekly, March 3, 1920; UP056.001.011.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.31 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 10, 1920; UP056.001.011.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.29 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 17, 1920; UP056.001.011.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.21 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 24, 1920; UP056.001.011.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.46 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 31, 1920; UP056.001.011.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.52 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 7, 1920; UP056.001.011.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.41 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 28, 1920; UP056.001.011.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.34 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 5, 1920; UP056.001.011.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.78 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 12, 1920; UP056.001.011.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.95 Megabytes (Box 11)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Alpha Xi Delta; Alumni field day
  - Tufts Weekly, May 19, 1920; UP056.001.011.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.57 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 26, 1920; UP056.001.011.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.59 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 2, 1920; UP056.001.011.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.00 Megabytes (Box 11)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 23, 1920; UP056.001.011.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.50 Megabytes (Box 11)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Commencement Issue; Alumni field day
  - Tufts Weekly, September 29, 1920; UP056.001.012.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.90 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 6, 1920; UP056.001.012.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.34 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 13, 1920; UP056.001.012.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.68 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 20, 1920; UP056.001.012.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.81 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 27, 1920; UP056.001.012.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.11 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 3, 1920; UP056.001.012.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.17 Megabytes (Box 12)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni] to form cheering section for Detroit game
  - Tufts Weekly, November 10, 1920; UP056.001.012.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.74 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 17, 1920; UP056.001.012.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.09 Megabytes (Box 12)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Academic Honors 1913-1920, pp. 1,4.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 24, 1920; UP056.001.012.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.14 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 1, 1920; UP056.001.012.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.05 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 8, 1920; UP056.001.012.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.67 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 15, 1920; UP056.001.012.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.00 Megabytes (Box 12)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, January 12, 1921; UP056.001.012.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.38 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 19, 1921; UP056.001.012.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.26 Megabytes (Box 12)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni] Four Tufts men in Massachusetts State Legislature
  - Tufts Weekly, January 26, 1921; UP056.001.012.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.45 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 9, 1921; UP056.001.012.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.15 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 16, 1921; UP056.001.012.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.56 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 23, 1921; UP056.001.012.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.99 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 2, 1921; UP056.001.012.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 10.64 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 9, 1921; UP056.001.012.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.54 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 16, 1921; UP056.001.012.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.38 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 23, 1921; UP056.001.012.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.52 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 30, 1921; UP056.001.012.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.37 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 6, 1921; UP056.001.012.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.97 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 27, 1921; UP056.001.012.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.25 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 4, 1921; UP056.001.012.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.51 Megabytes (Box 12)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Alpha Tau Omega. Alpha Xi Delta; [Alumni] Golf Tournament, p3
  - Tufts Weekly, May 11, 1921; UP056.001.012.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.18 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 18, 1921; UP056.001.012.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.42 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 25, 1921; UP056.001.012.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.33 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 1, 1921; UP056.001.012.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.72 Megabytes (Box 12)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni association] Alumni day
  - Tufts Weekly, June 8, 1921; UP056.001.012.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.54 Megabytes (Box 12)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 22, 1921; UP056.001.012.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.84 Megabytes (Box 12)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Alumni association meetings
  - Tufts Weekly, September 28, 1921; UP056.001.013.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.35 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 5, 1921; UP056.001.013.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.68 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 12, 1921; UP056.001.013.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.27 Megabytes (Box 13)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. All Around Club; American association of engineers [Tufts college association of engineers]
  - Tufts Weekly, October 19, 1921; UP056.001.013.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.42 Megabytes (Box 13)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [American association of engineers] Tufts college association of engineers
  - Tufts Weekly, October 26, 1921; UP056.001.013.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.47 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 2, 1921; UP056.001.013.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.10 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 9, 1921; UP056.001.013.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.67 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 16, 1921; UP056.001.013.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.78 Megabytes (Box 13)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Academic Honors 1921-1932, pp. 1,8. Alpha Tau Omega. [American association of engineers] Tufts college association of engineers
  - Tufts Weekly, November 23, 1921; UP056.001.013.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.19 Megabytes (Box 13)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. All Around Club. [American association of engineers] Tufts college association of engineers
  - Tufts Weekly, November 30, 1921; UP056.001.013.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.24 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 7, 1921; UP056.001.013.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.61 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 14, 1921; UP056.001.013.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.33 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 11, 1922; UP056.001.013.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.42 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 25, 1922; UP056.001.013.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.52 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 25, 1922; UP056.001.013.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.14 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 8, 1922; UP056.001.013.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.34 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 15, 1922; UP056.001.013.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.68 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 22, 1922; UP056.001.013.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.96 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 1, 1922; UP056.001.013.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.28 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 8, 1922; UP056.001.013.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.76 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 15, 1922; UP056.001.013.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.82 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 22, 1922; UP056.001.013.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.05 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 29, 1922; UP056.001.013.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 10.38 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 5, 1922; UP056.001.013.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.96 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 26, 1922; UP056.001.013.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.36 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 3, 1922; UP056.001.013.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.45 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 10, 1922; UP056.001.013.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 10.99 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 17, 1922; UP056.001.013.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.22 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 24, 1922; UP056.001.013.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.41 Megabytes (Box 13)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. C.A. Adams resigned as professor of mechanical engineering. p. 7 All Around Club.
  - Tufts Weekly, May 31, 1922; UP056.001.013.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.43 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 7, 1922; UP056.001.013.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 10.09 Megabytes (Box 13)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 19, 1922; UP056.001.013.00033; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.71 Megabytes (Box 13)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Commencement Issue; Alumni day photos, pp 80-81
  - Tufts Weekly, September 27, 1922; UP056.001.014.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.25 Megabytes (Box 14)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Admissions, 1922-23] Entrance Requirements.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 4, 1922; UP056.001.014.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.31 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 11, 1922; UP056.001.014.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.53 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 18, 1922; UP056.001.014.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.83 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 25, 1922; UP056.001.014.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.46 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 1, 1922; UP056.001.014.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.11 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 8, 1922; UP056.001.014.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.80 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 15, 1922; UP056.001.014.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.92 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 22, 1922; UP056.001.014.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.93 Megabytes (Box 14)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Academic Honors 1921-1932, pp. 1,8; John Coleman Adams. Death of, June 22, 1922.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 29, 1922; UP056.001.014.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.51 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 3, 1922; UP056.001.014.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.40 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 13, 1922; UP056.001.014.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.31 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 10, 1923; UP056.001.014.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.21 Megabytes (Box 14)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. All Around Club. Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, January 17, 1923; UP056.001.014.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.35 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 31, 1923; UP056.001.014.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.19 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 7, 1923; UP056.001.014.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.43 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 14, 1923; UP056.001.014.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.16 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 21, 1923; UP056.001.014.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.16 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 28, 1923; UP056.001.014.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 10.96 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 7, 1923; UP056.001.014.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.40 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 14, 1923; UP056.001.014.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.83 Megabytes (Box 14)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 21, 1923; UP056.001.014.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.66 Megabytes (Box 14)